<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Video &#8211; News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/category/video/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 16:40:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Anti-austerity protest in Germany</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/anti-austerity-protest-in-germany/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/anti-austerity-protest-in-germany/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 10:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Video]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Germany]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[protest]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=87</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Germany’s opposition parties backed on Thursday a major anti-austerity rally organized by the pan-European Blockupy movement in Frankfurt on Wednesday and criticized the German government for its attempts to discredit the protest. The main opposition Left Party’s co-chair, Katja Kipping, said that more than 20,000 demonstrators peacefully protested the EU’s austerity measures and the inauguration of the new [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="col-md-10">
<div>
<div class="detay-icerik">
<div>
<p>Germany’s opposition parties backed on <a href="https://www.aa.com.tr/en/politics/german-opposition-backs-anti-austerity-protest/en/world/480190--germany-clashes-as-thousands-rally-against-austerity" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Thursday a major anti-austerity rally organized by the pan-European Blockupy</a> movement in Frankfurt on Wednesday and criticized the German government for its attempts to discredit the protest.</p>
<p>The main opposition Left Party’s co-chair, Katja Kipping, said that more than 20,000 demonstrators peacefully protested the EU’s austerity measures and the inauguration of the new €1.3 billion ($1.4 billion) European Central Bank headquarters in Frankfurt.</p>
<p>“The overwhelming majority of people who took to the streets in Frankfurt yesterday wanted to demonstrate decisively but also peacefully against the austerity measures and they wanted to demonstrate that another Europe was possible,” Kipping said Thursday at a special session of the German parliament, which was scheduled to discuss the events of yesterday.</p>
<p>Hundreds of protesters were arrested and scores of police officers injured in Frankfurt on Wednesday after clashes that broke out in the early hours of the protests.</p>
<p>Some protesters set up barricades on the streets while others set fire to police cars during the clashes.  Organizers blamed the police for provoking violence.</p>
<p>Kipping distanced herself from the groups that used violence and underlined that these were a minority.</p>
<p>She dismissed government claims that the organizers planned the violent actions in Frankfurt.</p>
<p>Kipping said that the organizers of the protest clearly denounced violence and also worked to defuse tensions during the day.</p>
<p>“The aim of the protests was to clearly demonstrate to the European Central Bank that the opening of such a new, luxury headquarters could only be a source of protest, not celebration,” Kipping stressed.</p>
<p>Opposition Green Party lawmaker Irene Mihalic criticized Chancellor Angela Merkel’s ruling Christian Democrat bloc for blaming all the demonstrators for the violence and not differentiating between peaceful protestors and small, violent groups.</p>
<p>“Now you are trying to discredit the whole protest movement which also includes members of trade unions and democratic parties. You argue that they are all activists who are ready to use violence, who are abusing the right to protest. Then how can you explain the peaceful demonstration of thousands of people in the afternoon in Frankfurt’s city center,” Mihalic said at the parliament.</p>
<p>She also called on the Blockupy movement to clearly distance itself from any group that views the use of violence as legitimate.</p>
<p>Germany’s interior minister Thomas de Maiziere blamed the organizers on Thursday for the clashes in Frankfurt, claiming that these groups planned the violent actions weeks before.</p>
<p>“One who behaves in this manner and abuses freedoms and rights clearly crosses borders that we as a state of the rule of law cannot tolerate,” de Maiziere told lawmakers in parliament.</p>
<p>De Maiziere said 150 police officers were injured during the protests, 55 police cars were damaged and seven others were set on fire.</p>
<p>The pan-European Blockupy movement, an alliance of around 90 anti-globalization and anti-racist political parties, said that more than 200 protestors were injured during the clashes. The movement claimed police provoked protesters through their use of heavy security measures and deliberate use of tear gas.</p>
<p>The movement includes activist groups such as Attac, which advocates the taxing of financial transactions, Verdi, Germany&#8217;s second-biggest union which has more than two million members, and German political party Die Linke (The Left), which currently holds more than 10 percent of the country&#8217;s parliamentary seats.</p>
<p>Greek leftist party Syriza, which was elected in January, is also a member of the movement which argues ECB policies are pushing for balanced budgets at the expense of poor people and the middle classes across Europe.</p>
<p>Blockupy highlights the harsh economic measures imposed on heavily indebted Greece since 2010 by the &#8220;troika,&#8221; which is comprised of the ECB, European Commission and the International Monetary Fund, as an example of unacceptable and destructive economic practices.</p>
<p><span class="detay-foto-editor"><a href="https://www.aa.com.tr/en/p/subscription/1001" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Anadolu Agency website contains only a portion of the news stories offered to subscribers in the AA News Broadcasting System (HAS), and in summarized form. <b>Please contact us for subscription options.</b></a></span></div>
<div class="detay-paylas">
<h6>Related topics</h6>
<div></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="col-xl-2 col-lg-2 col-md-12 col-sm-12 detay-gundemdekiler p-sm-0 pl-md-3 pl-lg-3 pl-xl-3">
<div class="sticky-top donotprint">
<div>
<div class="analiz-baslikicon"><img src="https://cdnassets.aa.com.tr/assets/newVersion/images/analiz.png" alt="Analysis" /></div>
<div class="analiz-baslikbg"><a href="https://www.aa.com.tr/en/world">World</a></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/anti-austerity-protest-in-germany/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Avengers: Age of Ultron trailer</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/avengers-age-of-ultron-trailer/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/avengers-age-of-ultron-trailer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 10:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Video]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avengers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=94</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When Tony Stark jumpstarts a dormant peacekeeping program, things go awry and Earth’s Mightiest Heroes, including Iron Man, Captain America, Thor, The Incredible Hulk, Black Widow and Hawkeye, are put to the ultimate test as they battle to save the planet from destruction at the hands of the villainous Ultron.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe loading="lazy" title="Age of Ultron Trailers Chronological Edit" width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/eUuDYSoGJ3I?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>When Tony Stark jumpstarts a dormant peacekeeping program, things go awry and Earth’s Mightiest Heroes, including Iron Man, Captain America, Thor, The Incredible Hulk, Black Widow and Hawkeye, are put to the ultimate test as they battle to save the planet from destruction at the hands of the villainous Ultron.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/avengers-age-of-ultron-trailer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kendrick Lamar&#8217;s new album breaks record for Spotify streams</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/kendrick-lamars-new-album-breaks-record-for-spotify-streams/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/kendrick-lamars-new-album-breaks-record-for-spotify-streams/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 08:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Video]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[album]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lamar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spotify]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=33</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Kendrick Lamar&#8217;s new album To Pimp A Butterfly has broken global streaming records on Spotify. The album, which was unexpectedly released early this week (March 16), was streamed more than 9.6 million times on the service on its first day, setting a new record. The previous record holder for the highest number of global streams [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe loading="lazy" title="Kendrick Lamar - i (Official Video)" width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8aShfolR6w8?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<div class="grid">
<div class="grid__cell unit-2-3--desktop">
<div class="article-content">
<p>Kendrick Lamar&#8217;s new album To Pimp A Butterfly has broken global streaming records on Spotify.</p>
<p>The album, which was unexpectedly released early this week (March 16), was streamed more than 9.6 million times on the service on its first day, setting a new record.</p>
<p>The previous record holder for the highest number of global streams in a single day was Michael Buble&#8217;s Christmas, which notched up 9.5 million streams on Christmas Eve 2014.</p>
<p>To Pimp A Butterfly, which includes the Top 20 hit I, was originally slated for release on March 23. The album was then seemingly released in error on Monday after a representative for the rapper tweeted it was put by &#8220;mistake&#8221;.</p>
<p>The record marks Lamar&#8217;s second LP after 2012&#8217;s Good Kid M.A.A.D City, which peaked at Number 16 on the Official Albums Chart.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/kendrick-lamars-new-album-breaks-record-for-spotify-streams/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>&#8216;Game of Thrones&#8217; Season 5</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/game-of-thrones-season-5/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/game-of-thrones-season-5/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 07:43:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Video]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trailer]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=12</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wViILXQfX7Y Tincidunt varius sequi, integer magna ac, donec curabitur. Rhoncus sed. Lectus vitae augue, mauris tincidunt. Ut nec fermentum, dolor vestibulum. Nunc neque tincidunt, non dictumst tempus. Et id, duis sit arcu, felis porta donec. Proin tincidunt. Cum arcu pretium, sed sed. In nonummy, tempor molestie id, omnis tellus. A risus dolor, vitae et donec, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wViILXQfX7Y</p>
<p>Tincidunt varius sequi, integer magna ac, donec curabitur. Rhoncus sed. Lectus vitae augue, mauris tincidunt. Ut nec fermentum, dolor vestibulum. <a title="Testing the link styling" href="#">Nunc neque tincidunt, non dictumst tempus</a>. Et id, duis sit arcu, felis porta donec. Proin tincidunt.</p>
<p>Cum arcu pretium, sed sed. In nonummy, tempor molestie id, omnis tellus. A risus dolor, vitae et donec, mauris amet posuere. Donec in, nonummy dolor luctus. Laoreet ligula, pretium nisl eleifend, malesuada tincidunt cursus. Congue velit iaculis.</p>
<p>Euismod amet leo, cras et massa, eleifend egestas. Urna in nunc, nunc vivamus. Cum arcu pretium, sed sed. In nonummy, tempor molestie id, omnis tellus. A risus dolor, vitae et donec, mauris amet posuere. Donec in, nonummy dolor luctus. Laoreet ligula, pretium nisl eleifend, malesuada tincidunt cursus. Congue velit iaculis.</p>
<p><strong> Egestas at amet. Pharetra mauris. </strong>Mattis quam feugiat, iure ipsum. Vel fringilla, accumsan nam rhoncus, orci diam. Aenean sit sodales, urna porttitor. Nulla enim consequat, amet congue. Mauris vulputate, nonummy vel.</p>
<p>Euismod amet leo, cras et massa, eleifend egestas. Urna in nunc, nunc vivamus. Cum arcu pretium, sed sed. In nonummy, tempor molestie id, omnis tellus. A risus dolor, vitae et donec, mauris amet posuere. Donec in, nonummy dolor luctus. Laoreet ligula, pretium nisl eleifend, malesuada tincidunt cursus. Congue velit iaculis.</p>
<blockquote><p>Tincidunt varius sequi, integer magna ac, donec curabitur. Rhoncus sed. Lectus vitae augue, mauris tincidunt. Ut nec fermentum, dolor vestibulum. Nunc neque tincidunt, non dictumst tempus. Et id, duis sit arcu, felis porta donec. Proin tincidunt.</p>
<p><strong> Egestas at amet. Pharetra mauris. </strong>Mattis quam feugiat, iure ipsum. Vel fringilla, accumsan nam rhoncus, orci diam. Aenean sit sodales, urna porttitor. Nulla enim consequat, amet congue. Mauris vulputate, nonummy vel.</p></blockquote>
<p>Phasellus lorem aliquam, pede morbi, nulla sed. Urna ut a. Mattis viverra dignissim, suspendisse risus, felis a. Sit nec. Sit egestas condimentum. Tempor quisque sit, commodo justo consequat. Augue fermentum, est vulputate et, purus et. Tincidunt quam enim, ac a pede.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/game-of-thrones-season-5/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
