<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>featured &#8211; News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/tag/featured/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 16:18:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>What is the best smartwatch?</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/what-is-the-best-smartwatch/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/what-is-the-best-smartwatch/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 08:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Tech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smartwatch]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=16</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Track your activities and monitor your health with the best smartwatch. This wristwatch-slash-miniature companion to your smartphone is a useful tool especially if you&#8217;re trying to lead a healthy, active lifestyle or you&#8217;re on a wellness path. The more advanced models can even assist you in keeping an eye on some health concerns. Finding the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Track your activities and monitor your health with the best smartwatch. This wristwatch-slash-miniature companion to your smartphone is a useful tool especially if you&#8217;re trying to lead a healthy, active lifestyle or you&#8217;re on a wellness path. The more advanced models can even assist you in keeping an eye on some health concerns.</p>
<p>Finding the absolute best smartwatch for you is vital. Not only are there many on the market, but their features and functionalities – as well as size, shape, and <a class="hawk-link-parsed" href="https://www.techradar.com/news/best-phone" data-component-tracked="1">smartphone</a> compatibility – differ as well. And, you don&#8217;t want to end up with one that won&#8217;t meet your demands or pay a lot more for one that&#8217;s a bit of an overkill for your minimal needs.</p>
<aside class="hawk-nest hawk-processed" data-render-type="fte" data-skip="dealsy" data-widget-type="seasonal" data-widget-id="0a2e9bc5-9d01-4594-8cbe-f03c4c41ccd4" data-result="missing" data-feat-ref="hawk-id-0"></aside>
<p>We at TechRadar have tested and reviewed most smartwatch releases out there, from the more prevalent <a class="hawk-link-parsed" href="https://www.techradar.com/news/best-apple-watch" data-component-tracked="1">Apple Watches</a> and older <a class="hawk-link-parsed" href="https://www.techradar.com/news/best-samsung-smartwatch-finding-the-right-tizen-wearable-for-you" data-component-tracked="1">Samsung smartwatches</a> to Fitbit&#8217;s offerings and <a class="hawk-link-parsed" href="https://www.techradar.com/news/best-wear-os-watch" data-component-tracked="1">Wear OS watches</a> from brands like Fossil and Mobvoi. And, we&#8217;re here to guide you in choosing the most ideal smartwatch for you by gathering the best we&#8217;ve tested and ranking them here according to budget, use, and features.</p>
<p>For each entry though we&#8217;ve included a full specs list, along with an overview from our review and the key good and bad points. We&#8217;ve also included our price comparison tool so that you grab the best price available on the smartwatch you want. That way, you won&#8217;t have to do much research to round the choices down.</p>
<div class="van_vid_carousel vid-present">
<div class="van_vid_carousel__padding">
<div class="van_vid_carousel__container">
<div class="future__jwplayer--carousel">
<div class="jw-carousel"></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>If you do want to learn more though, make sure to tap through to our full review of each smartwatch. And make sure to check back soon, because new wearables keep on arriving.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/what-is-the-best-smartwatch/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Uber banned in Germany</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/uber-banned-in-germany/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/uber-banned-in-germany/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 08:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uber]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=46</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A German court banned Uber from operating its ride-hailing services in Germany today for lacking the licence necessary to offer transport services using rental cars. Uber is active in seven German cities and works exclusively with car rental companies and their drivers. It can appeal to a higher court and will continue to drive in [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A German court banned Uber from operating its ride-hailing services in Germany today for lacking the licence necessary to offer transport services using rental cars.</p>
<p>Uber is active in seven German cities and works exclusively with car rental companies and their drivers. It can appeal to a higher court and will continue to drive in Germany for the time being.</p>
<div class="notice-header  notice-header--is-full-content-width notice-header--is-bordered">
<div id="dsk-box-ad-d" data-google-query-id="COnllqzth_kCFVwMaAgdjoEA-w">
<div class="teads-inread">
<div>
<div id="teads0" class="teads-player"><span style="font-size: revert; color: initial;">“We will assess the court’s ruling and determine next steps to ensure our services in Germany continue,” the company said. </span></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>Uber will change the way it operates in Europe’s largest economy and is considering taking legal action against the ruling.</p>
<p>Taxi Deutschland, a national taxi provider in Germany, brought the case and said it would seek immediate provisional enforcement.</p>
<p>“We are happy that we were right today. Once again it was judicially determined that the same law applies to small and large companies. Uber has no authorisation for passenger transportation in Germany,” the cooperative said.</p>
<p>The presiding judge said: “From a passenger’s point of view, Uber provides the service itself and is therefore an entrepreneur.”</p>
<div class="notice-header  notice-header--is-full-content-width notice-header--is-bordered">
<div id="dsk-box-ad-f" data-google-query-id="CMnGlKzth_kCFdoAaAgd63UIBA"></div>
</div>
<p>Uber has been unable to match customers with drivers using their own cars in Germany since 2015.</p>
<p>This is the latest in a series of unfortunate events for the ride-sharing app.</p>
<p>Last month Uber lost its licence to operate in London after Transport for London (TfL) identified a “pattern of failures” by the company were putting customers at risk.</p>
<p>Authorities found that more than 14,000 trips were taken with drivers who had faked their identity on the firm’s app.</p>
<p>Jamie Heywood, Regional General Manager for Northern &amp; Eastern Europe, Uber said: “We are appealing TfL’s decision. Safety is our top priority which is why we have robust systems and processes in place.”</p>
<div class="notice-header  notice-header--is-full-content-width notice-header--is-bordered">
<div id="dsk-box-ad-g" data-google-query-id="CPjZha3th_kCFVBVDQodxrUIVg">
<div id="google_ads_iframe_/134702932,4152489/0367-cityam.com_5__container__"><span style="font-size: revert; color: initial;">Speaking on the driver identification issue, Heywood said: “We uncovered this issue, we raised this with TfL and put in place an effective fix.”</span></div>
</div>
</div>
<p>In a statement last month, TfL said: “Despite addressing some of these issues, <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk/tfl">TfL</a> does not have confidence that similar issues will not reoccur in the future, which has led it to conclude that the company is not fit and proper at this time.”</p>
<p>This came after California ruled in September that Uber has to consider drivers employees rather than contractors, meaning it must meet the minimum wage and provide sick pay.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/uber-banned-in-germany/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Facebook buys TheFind</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/facebook-buys-thefind/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/facebook-buys-thefind/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 08:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Facebook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TheFind]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=67</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Facebook today announced it has acquired personalized shopping search engine TheFind to help improve its commerce ads. TheFind had raised $26 million from Lightspeed and Redpoint since getting off the ground around 2005, but will now be shut down. Some, but not all, members of the team are joining Facebook. TheFind’s product allowed people to get customized recommendations for [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p id="speakable-summary">Facebook today announced it has acquired personalized shopping search engine <a href="http://www.thefind.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">TheFind</a> to help improve its commerce ads. TheFind had raised <a href="https://www.crunchbase.com/organization/thefind" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$26 million</a> from Lightspeed and Redpoint since getting off the ground around 2005, but will now be shut down. Some, but not all, members of the team are joining Facebook.</p>
<p>TheFind’s product allowed people to get customized recommendations for products while searching through its massive database of products. A user could enter somewhat generic terms like “black sweater” and then compare prices on black sweaters from a wide array of retailers aggregated by TheFind. They could also discover places to buy their chosen product locally if they want it immediately.</p>
<p>Just last month, Facebook launched a <a href="https://beta.techcrunch.com/2015/02/17/facebook-product-ads/#fTw4kd:NC8B">special ad unit</a> designed to highlight specific products a merchant is trying to sell. TheFind could help Facebook better match not just a company to a user, but make sure the products shown in the ads are things they’re likely to buy.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-1132117" src="https://beta.techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/screen-shot-2015-03-13-at-3-49-57-pm.png?w=680" sizes="(max-width: 680px) 100vw, 680px" srcset="https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/screen-shot-2015-03-13-at-3-49-57-pm.png 1010w, https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/screen-shot-2015-03-13-at-3-49-57-pm.png?resize=150,72 150w, https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/screen-shot-2015-03-13-at-3-49-57-pm.png?resize=300,144 300w, https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/screen-shot-2015-03-13-at-3-49-57-pm.png?resize=768,370 768w, https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/screen-shot-2015-03-13-at-3-49-57-pm.png?resize=680,327 680w, https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/screen-shot-2015-03-13-at-3-49-57-pm.png?resize=50,24 50w" alt="Screen Shot 2015-03-13 at 3.49.57 PM" width="680" height="327" /></p>
<p>Over the past few years, Facebook had increasingly courted big-brand advertisers and developers seeking to buy app install ads. But with the new product ads and this acquisition, it seems intent on squeezing more cash out of direct marketers, e-commerce companies, and fashion brands.</p>
<p>Facebook tells me:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We’re excited to welcome TheFind to Facebook. TheFind’s talented team has built a successful search engine that connects people to products. Together, we believe we can make the Facebook ads experience even more relevant and better for consumers. Our business is about connecting people with the topics, companies, brands, and increasingly products they care about and we look forward to doing that with TheFind on board.”</p></blockquote>
<p>TheFind writes:</p>
<blockquote><p><em>We are joining Facebook!</em></p>
<p><strong> </strong>For the last nine years, we’ve worked hard to bring you a shopping experience that’s easy, efficient and fun – searching all the stores on the web to find just the right products you’re looking to buy.</p>
<p>We are now starting our next chapter by combining forces with Facebook to do even more for consumers. Facebook’s resources and platform give us the opportunity to scale our expertise in product sourcing to the over 1 billion people that use the platform.</p>
<p>Key members of our team are joining the company and will be working hard to integrate our technology to make the ads you see on Facebook every day better and more relevant to you.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, this means we will be taking our search engine offline in the next few weeks.</p>
<p>Thank you for your loyalty and for making this a fun journey for all of us!</p></blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/facebook-buys-thefind/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
