<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Wonder Woman &#8211; News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/tag/wonder-woman/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 15:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The original Wonder Woman</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/the-original-wonder-woman/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/the-original-wonder-woman/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 09:35:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wonder Woman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=70</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[“Noted Psychologist Revealed as Author of Best-Selling ‘Wonder Woman,’” read the astonishing headline. In the summer of 1942, a press release from the New York offices of All-American Comics turned up at newspapers, magazines and radio stations all over the United States. The identity of Wonder Woman’s creator had been “at first kept secret,” it [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>“Noted Psychologist Revealed as Author of Best-Selling ‘Wonder Woman,’” read the astonishing headline. In the summer of 1942, a press release from the New York offices of All-American Comics turned up at newspapers, magazines and radio stations all over the United States. The identity of Wonder Woman’s creator had been “at first kept secret,” it said, but the time had come to make a shocking announcement: “the author of ‘Wonder Woman’ is Dr. William Moulton Marston, internationally famous psychologist.” The truth about Wonder Woman had come out at last.</p>
<p>Or so, at least, it was made to appear. But, really, the name of Wonder Woman’s creator was the least of her secrets.</p>
<p>Wonder Woman is the most popular female comic-book superhero of all time. Aside from Superman and Batman, no other comic-book character has lasted as long. Generations of girls have carried their sandwiches to school in Wonder Woman lunchboxes. Like every other superhero, Wonder Woman has a secret identity. Unlike every other superhero, she also has a secret history.</p>
<p>In one episode, a newspaper editor named Brown, desperate to discover Wonder Woman’s past, assigns a team of reporters to chase her down; she easily escapes them. Brown, gone half mad, is committed to a hospital. Wonder Woman disguises herself as a nurse and brings him a scroll. “This parchment seems to be the history of that girl you call ‘Wonder Woman’!” she tells him. “A strange, veiled woman left it with me.” Brown leaps out of bed and races back to the city desk, where he cries out, parchment in hand, “Stop the presses! I’ve got the history of Wonder Woman!” But Wonder Woman’s secret history isn’t written on parchment. Instead, it lies buried in boxes and cabinets and drawers, in thousands of documents, housed in libraries, archives and collections spread all over the United States, including the private papers of creator Marston—papers that, before I saw them, had never before been seen by anyone outside of Marston’s family.</p>
<p>The veil that has shrouded Wonder Woman’s past for seven decades hides beneath it a crucial story about comic books and superheroes and censorship and feminism. As Marston once put it, “Frankly, Wonder Woman is psychological propaganda for the new type of woman who, I believe, should rule the world.”</p>
<div class="binding-box">
<div class="embedly-retail"></div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/the-original-wonder-woman/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
