<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Business &#8211; News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/category/business/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 16:41:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Ryanair could offer $15 flights from the US to Europe</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/ryanair-could-offer-15-flights-from-the-us-to-europe/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/ryanair-could-offer-15-flights-from-the-us-to-europe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 10:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ryanair]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=84</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ryanair, known mostly for its risqué ads and abysmal customer service, has announced it plans to expand to the U.S. The budget airline, which primarily operates throughout Western Europe, is trying to capture a slice of the hugely profitable transatlantic market dominated by legacy carriers. “The board of Ryanair, like any PLC, have approved the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="speakable">Ryanair, known mostly for its risqué ads and abysmal customer service, has announced it plans to expand to the U.S.</p>
<p class="speakable">The budget airline, which primarily operates throughout Western Europe, is trying to capture a slice of the hugely profitable transatlantic market dominated by legacy carriers.</p>
<p>“The board of Ryanair, like any PLC, have approved the business plans for future growth, including transatlantic. We are talking to manufacturers about long-haul aircraft but can’t comment further on this,” a spokesperson for the airline told <a href="http://skift.com/2015/03/17/thus-the-fight-begins-ryanair-is-coming-to-the-u-s/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Skift.</a> “European consumers want lower cost travel to the USA and the same for Americans coming to Europe. We see it as a logical development in the European market.”</p>
<p>Ryanair said it would offer promotional fares—as low as £10 or $15 —from select American cities to London to shake up the old guard.  But don&#8217;t get too excited.  Regular prices would run about $200 to $300, and then there are the slew of fees, including charges to reserve seats and airline ticket printing.</p>
<p>The airline plans to offer flights between as many as 14 European cities and 12 to 14 U.S. cities. While the plan is still in its infant stages, we could see Ryanair stateside in about five years.</p>
<p>According to IATA data, the transatlantic market is considered the “jewel of the aviation industry,” accounting for over 16 percent of global airline traffic and a whopping 55 percent of revenue.  Despite an open-skies deal signed between the European Union and the U.S. in 2007, budget carriers have not figured out a model that allows them to compete.</p>
<p>But flying across Europe, with its notoriously cramped seats and scaled down amenities, may not be like flying across the pond.</p>
<p>The carrier plans to buy a fleet of 50 brand new aircraft that will feature a business class section, which doesn&#8217;t exist on its European service.  These could include fuel-efficient, modern planes, such as the Boeing Dreamliner and Airbus A350, but it all depends on when the carrier could get them, because manufacturing demand for these aircraft has soared.</p>
<p>But, Ryanair may be dependent on the use of second-tier airports—usually miles away from the major city hubs—which allows for greater airline efficiency and helps significantly cut costs.  U.S. airline consolidation has reduced capacity at these smaller markets, but customers, especially business travelers, may see these locations as less desirable.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/ryanair-could-offer-15-flights-from-the-us-to-europe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Indian Music And Movie Streaming &#8211; Raising $100 Million</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/indian-music-and-movie-streaming-raising-100-million/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/indian-music-and-movie-streaming-raising-100-million/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 09:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Indian]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=73</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The promise of mobile in India is attracting venture capital at a rate never seen before. The latest deal of note involves Hungama, a media company that provides music, videos and movies on mobile, desktop and beyond, which is on the cusp of raising more than $100 million. Sources close to the media company told TechCrunch that it [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p id="speakable-summary">The promise of mobile in <a href="https://beta.techcrunch.com/tag/india/">India is attracting venture capital</a> at a rate never seen before. The latest deal of note involves <a href="http://www.hungama.com/#/home" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Hungama</a>, a media company that provides music, videos and movies on mobile, desktop and beyond, which is on the cusp of raising more than $100 million.</p>
<p>Sources close to the media company told TechCrunch that it is in “advanced” talks with existing investors Intel Capital and Bessemer Venture Partners, which fronted <a href="http://www.vccircle.com/news/technology/2014/07/04/hungama-raises-40m-led-bessemer-venture-partners" target="_blank" rel="noopener">a $40 million raise</a> last summer. <a href="http://www.medianama.com/2012/10/223-intel-capital-invests-in-hungama-digital-40-million-in-10-companies/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Intel Capital invested an undisclosed sum</a> in the business in 2012.</p>
<p>Hungama was founded in 2005 as a marketing and communications agency that offered services such as interactive gaming, lead promotion and community building for brands. Eying the growth of mobile, it branched out to entertainment in 2009, and today it is arguably India’s most prominent player in that space. (The original, marketing-focused side of the business was <a href="http://www.medianama.com/2012/06/223-jwt-wpp-hungama/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">sold to WPP in 2012</a>.)</p>
<p>The company is long profitable and the funding round closed last year was for growth. It’s the same story this time around, only with loftier targets. TechCrunch understands that this soon-to-be-completed round will be used to grow the company’s footprint on mobile, tapping into <a href="https://beta.techcrunch.com/2015/03/15/tapping-into-the-growth-of-indias-emerging-mobile-markets/">the vast growth in adoption of smartphones that is expected in India</a>.</p>
<p>More specifically, we understand that Hungama will invest to develop its technology, platforms and increase its content libraries. Sources at the company also revealed that the money could be used to acquire other market players.</p>
<p>The total audience for Hungama’s services hit 48 million users in February. Of that figure, a whopping 43 million consumed content on a mobile device, with 13.8 million paying for some form of content across its platform. Hungama’s services were used by 227 million consumers during its last financial year, with around one-third spending money in some way.</p>
<p>Those numbers are impressive, and Hungama relationship with India’s telecom operators is a key part of its mainstream reach. Not only do those alliances provide a platform to distribute services across the country, but they allow Hungama to offer song downloads unlike other rivals. In a country where the speed of mobile data connections varies wildly and the overwhelming major of consumers are on pre-paid mobile tariffs, that’s a crucial feature. (The demand for off-network media is such that <a href="https://beta.techcrunch.com/2014/12/10/youtube-offline-india-indonesia-philippines/">YouTube recently introduced offline playback in India</a> and two other markets.)</p>
<div class="midarticle-ad-wrapper">
<div class="container__access-control">
<div class="ad-unit  ">
<div>
<div id="tc-ad-mobile_midarticle1-1134202-pos-1" class="ad-unit__ad ad-unit__mobile_midarticle1">
<div id="jacPosition_mobile_midarticle1-1134202-pos-1" class="jac-container">
<div></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>The company’s main competitors in the music streaming space in India include Times India-owned Gaana, Saavn — which <a href="https://beta.techcrunch.com/2015/01/21/saavn-11-million-mau/">recently hit 11 million monthly users</a> — and Rdio, which <a href="https://beta.techcrunch.com/2015/01/15/rdio-india/">entered India</a> in January having acquired Dhingana in 2014. There is also <a href="http://www.airtel.in/wynkmusic/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">operator Airtel’s Wynk service</a>.</p>
<p>Unlike these younger companies, Hungama goes beyond music to offer Netflix-like movies. With India’s music and film scene closely tied together, the company is betting that this synergy and its international catalog — which just <a href="http://www.medianama.com/2015/03/223-hungama-to-offer-disney-and-marvel-movies-on-demand/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">added Disney and Marvel</a> — will help it stand apart from the rest. <a href="https://beta.techcrunch.com/2015/02/09/internet-org-india/">Being included on Facebook’s free Internet.org portal</a>, which just arrived in India, doesn’t hurt too.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/indian-music-and-movie-streaming-raising-100-million/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple working on an Internet TV subscription service</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/apple-working-on-an-internet-tv-subscription-service/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/apple-working-on-an-internet-tv-subscription-service/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 09:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Apple TV]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=49</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tincidunt varius sequi, integer magna ac, donec curabitur. Rhoncus sed. Lectus vitae augue, mauris tincidunt. Ut nec fermentum, dolor vestibulum. Nunc neque tincidunt, non dictumst tempus. Et id, duis sit arcu, felis porta donec. Proin tincidunt. Cum arcu pretium, sed sed. In nonummy, tempor molestie id, omnis tellus. A risus dolor, vitae et donec, mauris [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tincidunt varius sequi, integer magna ac, donec curabitur. Rhoncus sed. Lectus vitae augue, mauris tincidunt. Ut nec fermentum, dolor vestibulum. <a title="Testing the link styling" href="#">Nunc neque tincidunt, non dictumst tempus</a>. Et id, duis sit arcu, felis porta donec. Proin tincidunt.</p>
<p>Cum arcu pretium, sed sed. In nonummy, tempor molestie id, omnis tellus. A risus dolor, vitae et donec, mauris amet posuere. Donec in, nonummy dolor luctus. Laoreet ligula, pretium nisl eleifend, malesuada tincidunt cursus. Congue velit iaculis.</p>
<p>Euismod amet leo, cras et massa, eleifend egestas. Urna in nunc, nunc vivamus. Cum arcu pretium, sed sed. In nonummy, tempor molestie id, omnis tellus. A risus dolor, vitae et donec, mauris amet posuere. Donec in, nonummy dolor luctus. Laoreet ligula, pretium nisl eleifend, malesuada tincidunt cursus. Congue velit iaculis.</p>
<p><strong> Egestas at amet. Pharetra mauris. </strong>Mattis quam feugiat, iure ipsum. Vel fringilla, accumsan nam rhoncus, orci diam. Aenean sit sodales, urna porttitor. Nulla enim consequat, amet congue. Mauris vulputate, nonummy vel.</p>
<p>Euismod amet leo, cras et massa, eleifend egestas. Urna in nunc, nunc vivamus. Cum arcu pretium, sed sed. In nonummy, tempor molestie id, omnis tellus. A risus dolor, vitae et donec, mauris amet posuere. Donec in, nonummy dolor luctus. Laoreet ligula, pretium nisl eleifend, malesuada tincidunt cursus. Congue velit iaculis.</p>
<blockquote><p>Tincidunt varius sequi, integer magna ac, donec curabitur. Rhoncus sed. Lectus vitae augue, mauris tincidunt. Ut nec fermentum, dolor vestibulum. Nunc neque tincidunt, non dictumst tempus. Et id, duis sit arcu, felis porta donec. Proin tincidunt.</p>
<p><strong> Egestas at amet. Pharetra mauris. </strong>Mattis quam feugiat, iure ipsum. Vel fringilla, accumsan nam rhoncus, orci diam. Aenean sit sodales, urna porttitor. Nulla enim consequat, amet congue. Mauris vulputate, nonummy vel.</p></blockquote>
<p>Phasellus lorem aliquam, pede morbi, nulla sed. Urna ut a. Mattis viverra dignissim, suspendisse risus, felis a. Sit nec. Sit egestas condimentum. Tempor quisque sit, commodo justo consequat. Augue fermentum, est vulputate et, purus et. Tincidunt quam enim, ac a pede.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/apple-working-on-an-internet-tv-subscription-service/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Uber banned in Germany</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/uber-banned-in-germany/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/uber-banned-in-germany/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 08:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uber]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=46</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A German court banned Uber from operating its ride-hailing services in Germany today for lacking the licence necessary to offer transport services using rental cars. Uber is active in seven German cities and works exclusively with car rental companies and their drivers. It can appeal to a higher court and will continue to drive in [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A German court banned Uber from operating its ride-hailing services in Germany today for lacking the licence necessary to offer transport services using rental cars.</p>
<p>Uber is active in seven German cities and works exclusively with car rental companies and their drivers. It can appeal to a higher court and will continue to drive in Germany for the time being.</p>
<div class="notice-header  notice-header--is-full-content-width notice-header--is-bordered">
<div id="dsk-box-ad-d" data-google-query-id="COnllqzth_kCFVwMaAgdjoEA-w">
<div class="teads-inread">
<div>
<div id="teads0" class="teads-player"><span style="font-size: revert; color: initial;">“We will assess the court’s ruling and determine next steps to ensure our services in Germany continue,” the company said. </span></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>Uber will change the way it operates in Europe’s largest economy and is considering taking legal action against the ruling.</p>
<p>Taxi Deutschland, a national taxi provider in Germany, brought the case and said it would seek immediate provisional enforcement.</p>
<p>“We are happy that we were right today. Once again it was judicially determined that the same law applies to small and large companies. Uber has no authorisation for passenger transportation in Germany,” the cooperative said.</p>
<p>The presiding judge said: “From a passenger’s point of view, Uber provides the service itself and is therefore an entrepreneur.”</p>
<div class="notice-header  notice-header--is-full-content-width notice-header--is-bordered">
<div id="dsk-box-ad-f" data-google-query-id="CMnGlKzth_kCFdoAaAgd63UIBA"></div>
</div>
<p>Uber has been unable to match customers with drivers using their own cars in Germany since 2015.</p>
<p>This is the latest in a series of unfortunate events for the ride-sharing app.</p>
<p>Last month Uber lost its licence to operate in London after Transport for London (TfL) identified a “pattern of failures” by the company were putting customers at risk.</p>
<p>Authorities found that more than 14,000 trips were taken with drivers who had faked their identity on the firm’s app.</p>
<p>Jamie Heywood, Regional General Manager for Northern &amp; Eastern Europe, Uber said: “We are appealing TfL’s decision. Safety is our top priority which is why we have robust systems and processes in place.”</p>
<div class="notice-header  notice-header--is-full-content-width notice-header--is-bordered">
<div id="dsk-box-ad-g" data-google-query-id="CPjZha3th_kCFVBVDQodxrUIVg">
<div id="google_ads_iframe_/134702932,4152489/0367-cityam.com_5__container__"><span style="font-size: revert; color: initial;">Speaking on the driver identification issue, Heywood said: “We uncovered this issue, we raised this with TfL and put in place an effective fix.”</span></div>
</div>
</div>
<p>In a statement last month, TfL said: “Despite addressing some of these issues, <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk/tfl">TfL</a> does not have confidence that similar issues will not reoccur in the future, which has led it to conclude that the company is not fit and proper at this time.”</p>
<p>This came after California ruled in September that Uber has to consider drivers employees rather than contractors, meaning it must meet the minimum wage and provide sick pay.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/uber-banned-in-germany/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Facebook buys TheFind</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/facebook-buys-thefind/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/facebook-buys-thefind/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 08:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Facebook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TheFind]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=67</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Facebook today announced it has acquired personalized shopping search engine TheFind to help improve its commerce ads. TheFind had raised $26 million from Lightspeed and Redpoint since getting off the ground around 2005, but will now be shut down. Some, but not all, members of the team are joining Facebook. TheFind’s product allowed people to get customized recommendations for [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p id="speakable-summary">Facebook today announced it has acquired personalized shopping search engine <a href="http://www.thefind.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">TheFind</a> to help improve its commerce ads. TheFind had raised <a href="https://www.crunchbase.com/organization/thefind" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$26 million</a> from Lightspeed and Redpoint since getting off the ground around 2005, but will now be shut down. Some, but not all, members of the team are joining Facebook.</p>
<p>TheFind’s product allowed people to get customized recommendations for products while searching through its massive database of products. A user could enter somewhat generic terms like “black sweater” and then compare prices on black sweaters from a wide array of retailers aggregated by TheFind. They could also discover places to buy their chosen product locally if they want it immediately.</p>
<p>Just last month, Facebook launched a <a href="https://beta.techcrunch.com/2015/02/17/facebook-product-ads/#fTw4kd:NC8B">special ad unit</a> designed to highlight specific products a merchant is trying to sell. TheFind could help Facebook better match not just a company to a user, but make sure the products shown in the ads are things they’re likely to buy.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-1132117" src="https://beta.techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/screen-shot-2015-03-13-at-3-49-57-pm.png?w=680" sizes="(max-width: 680px) 100vw, 680px" srcset="https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/screen-shot-2015-03-13-at-3-49-57-pm.png 1010w, https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/screen-shot-2015-03-13-at-3-49-57-pm.png?resize=150,72 150w, https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/screen-shot-2015-03-13-at-3-49-57-pm.png?resize=300,144 300w, https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/screen-shot-2015-03-13-at-3-49-57-pm.png?resize=768,370 768w, https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/screen-shot-2015-03-13-at-3-49-57-pm.png?resize=680,327 680w, https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/screen-shot-2015-03-13-at-3-49-57-pm.png?resize=50,24 50w" alt="Screen Shot 2015-03-13 at 3.49.57 PM" width="680" height="327" /></p>
<p>Over the past few years, Facebook had increasingly courted big-brand advertisers and developers seeking to buy app install ads. But with the new product ads and this acquisition, it seems intent on squeezing more cash out of direct marketers, e-commerce companies, and fashion brands.</p>
<p>Facebook tells me:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We’re excited to welcome TheFind to Facebook. TheFind’s talented team has built a successful search engine that connects people to products. Together, we believe we can make the Facebook ads experience even more relevant and better for consumers. Our business is about connecting people with the topics, companies, brands, and increasingly products they care about and we look forward to doing that with TheFind on board.”</p></blockquote>
<p>TheFind writes:</p>
<blockquote><p><em>We are joining Facebook!</em></p>
<p><strong> </strong>For the last nine years, we’ve worked hard to bring you a shopping experience that’s easy, efficient and fun – searching all the stores on the web to find just the right products you’re looking to buy.</p>
<p>We are now starting our next chapter by combining forces with Facebook to do even more for consumers. Facebook’s resources and platform give us the opportunity to scale our expertise in product sourcing to the over 1 billion people that use the platform.</p>
<p>Key members of our team are joining the company and will be working hard to integrate our technology to make the ads you see on Facebook every day better and more relevant to you.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, this means we will be taking our search engine offline in the next few weeks.</p>
<p>Thank you for your loyalty and for making this a fun journey for all of us!</p></blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/facebook-buys-thefind/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Windows 10 is coming to 190 countries this summer</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/windows-10-is-coming-to-190-countries-this-summer/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/windows-10-is-coming-to-190-countries-this-summer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 08:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Windows 10]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=27</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Times are changing in the PC space. Windows 10, the grand unification of Xbox, mobile, tablets, desktops, and laptops for Microsoft is due for release in the summer, in 190 countries and in 111 languages, the company states. So, all of that should be fun, no doubt. However, a bit of news that is more [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p id="c933" class="pw-post-body-paragraph jl jm ih jn b jo jp jq jr js jt ju jv jw jx jy jz ka kb kc kd ke kf kg kh ki ia gi" data-selectable-paragraph="">Times are changing in the PC space. Windows 10, the grand unification of Xbox, mobile, tablets, desktops, and laptops for Microsoft is due for release in the summer, in 190 countries and in 111 languages, the company states. So, all of that should be fun, no doubt.</p>
<p id="a709" class="pw-post-body-paragraph jl jm ih jn b jo jp jq jr js jt ju jv jw jx jy jz ka kb kc kd ke kf kg kh ki ia gi" data-selectable-paragraph="">However, a bit of news that is more interesting is the free upgrade for users on Windows 7 and 8 that includes <em class="kj">all</em> versions — genuine or otherwise (!). Terry Myerson, Microsoft’s Executive Vice President of Operating Systems, told <em class="kj">Reuters</em> that, “We are upgrading all qualified PCs, genuine and non-genuine, to Windows 10.”</p>
<p id="7338" class="pw-post-body-paragraph jl jm ih jn b jo jp jq jr js jt ju jv jw jx jy jz ka kb kc kd ke kf kg kh ki ia gi" data-selectable-paragraph="">The report was in regards to China, but considering “all qualified PCs” is a very broad term, this could also extend to other regions — and thus really make the adoption rate of Windows 10 immense, then luring the profits through the use of premium programs.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/windows-10-is-coming-to-190-countries-this-summer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Australia: controversial data retention laws</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/australia-controversial-data-retention-laws/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/australia-controversial-data-retention-laws/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 08:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Australia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[law]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=24</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Australia has passed a controversial security law that will require its internet and mobile phone providers to store customer data for two years. The government bill got Senate approval by 43 votes to 16, with the support of the opposition Labor party. Internet providers and and mobile phone networks will now be required to store [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00"><b class="ssrcss-hmf8ql-BoldText e5tfeyi3">Australia has passed a controversial security law that will require its internet and mobile phone providers to store customer data for two years.</b></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">The government bill got Senate approval by 43 votes to 16, with the support of the opposition Labor party.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">Internet providers and and mobile phone networks will now be required to store customers&#8217; metadata &#8211; the sender, recipient and time of emails and calls.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">Metadata does not include the content of an email or telephone call.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">The Green Party voted against the bill, along with six independent senators.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">A number of amendments proposed by Green and independent senators &#8211; including an increased requirement for warrants in order to access data &#8211; were defeated by the Senate.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div id="piano-inline1">
<div class="tp-container-inner"></div>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-dm4ypg-ComponentWrapper-HeadlineComponentWrapper e1xue1i89" data-component="subheadline-block">
<h2 id="Mass-surveillance" class="ssrcss-y2fd7s-StyledHeading e1fj1fc10" tabindex="-1"><span role="text">&#8216;Mass surveillance&#8217;</span></h2>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">The government has argued that the bill is necessary to help Australia&#8217;s security services fight domestic terrorism.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">&#8220;By passing this Bill, the parliament has ensured that our security and law enforcement agencies will continue to have access to the information they need to do their jobs,&#8221; said Attorney-General George Brandis and Communications Minister Malcolm Turnbull in a joint statement.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">&#8220;No responsible government can sit by while those who protect us lose access to vital information, particularly in the current high threat environment.&#8221;</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">But the legislation has been heavily criticised by privacy advocates, which have warned it could be open to abuse.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">Greens Party senator Scott Ludlam, who voted against the bill, described the new law as &#8220;a form of mass surveillance&#8221;.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">&#8220;Surveillance should be targeted, proportionate and levelled at serious criminals, organised crime and national security threats,&#8221; Mr Ludlam said. &#8220;This bill entrenches the opposite.&#8221;</p>
</div>
</div>
<div id="piano-inline2"></div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">The government has not released detailed costs for the scheme, but Prime Minister Tony Abbott last month estimated that it would cost internet providers and telecommunications firms about A$400m (£210m; $315m).</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">Mr Turnbull, who has championed the bill, told Sky News that the government had pledged to supply a &#8220;substantial&#8221; portion of the cost.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-dm4ypg-ComponentWrapper-HeadlineComponentWrapper e1xue1i89" data-component="subheadline-block">
<h2 id="Collection-gaps" class="ssrcss-y2fd7s-StyledHeading e1fj1fc10" tabindex="-1"><span role="text">Collection gaps</span></h2>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">The metadata retention rules do not extend to widely-used third-party email, video, and social media platforms such as Gmail, Hotmail, Facebook and Skype.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">Also exempt from metadata retention are internal email and telephone networks, such as those provided by corporate firms and universities.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">Speaking to Sky News on Wednesday, Australia&#8217;s Communications Minister Malcolm Turnbull listed a wide variety of platforms and apps that are exempt, including Whatsapp, Viber, and Signal.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">The gaps in services covered by the new law, and the government&#8217;s advertisement of communication services that are exempt, have raised questions over the bill&#8217;s potential efficacy as a counter-terror tool.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div id="piano-inline3"></div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">The legislation, which will come into effect in 2017, was also fiercely criticised by Australia&#8217;s media industry over its potential to compromise the ability of journalists to communicate securely with sources.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">The government was forced to add a Labor-sponsored amendment to the bill requiring security services to obtain a warrant before accessing journalists&#8217; metadata.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">Australia is part of the &#8220;five-eyes&#8221; intelligence-sharing network, along with the US, Canada, New Zealand, and the United Kingdom.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">The US already has laws under the Patriot Act allowing its National Security Agency (NSA) to collect metadata in bulk.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ssrcss-uf6wea-RichTextComponentWrapper e1xue1i86" data-component="text-block">
<div class="ssrcss-7uxr49-RichTextContainer e5tfeyi1">
<p class="ssrcss-1q0x1qg-Paragraph eq5iqo00">The NSA&#8217;s data collection sparked international debate in 2013 when details of the programme were leaked by contractor Edward Snowden.</p>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/australia-controversial-data-retention-laws/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Publishers combine forces to lure advertisers</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/publishers-combine-forces-to-lure-advertisers/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/publishers-combine-forces-to-lure-advertisers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 08:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=19</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tincidunt varius sequi, integer magna ac, donec curabitur. Rhoncus sed. Lectus vitae augue, mauris tincidunt. Ut nec fermentum, dolor vestibulum. Nunc neque tincidunt, non dictumst tempus. Et id, duis sit arcu, felis porta donec. Proin tincidunt. Cum arcu pretium, sed sed. In nonummy, tempor molestie id, omnis tellus. A risus dolor, vitae et donec, mauris [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tincidunt varius sequi, integer magna ac, donec curabitur. Rhoncus sed. Lectus vitae augue, mauris tincidunt. Ut nec fermentum, dolor vestibulum. <a title="Testing the link styling" href="#">Nunc neque tincidunt, non dictumst tempus</a>. Et id, duis sit arcu, felis porta donec. Proin tincidunt.</p>
<p>Cum arcu pretium, sed sed. In nonummy, tempor molestie id, omnis tellus. A risus dolor, vitae et donec, mauris amet posuere. Donec in, nonummy dolor luctus. Laoreet ligula, pretium nisl eleifend, malesuada tincidunt cursus. Congue velit iaculis.</p>
<p>Euismod amet leo, cras et massa, eleifend egestas. Urna in nunc, nunc vivamus. Cum arcu pretium, sed sed. In nonummy, tempor molestie id, omnis tellus. A risus dolor, vitae et donec, mauris amet posuere. Donec in, nonummy dolor luctus. Laoreet ligula, pretium nisl eleifend, malesuada tincidunt cursus. Congue velit iaculis.</p>
<p><strong> Egestas at amet. Pharetra mauris. </strong>Mattis quam feugiat, iure ipsum. Vel fringilla, accumsan nam rhoncus, orci diam. Aenean sit sodales, urna porttitor. Nulla enim consequat, amet congue. Mauris vulputate, nonummy vel.</p>
<p>Euismod amet leo, cras et massa, eleifend egestas. Urna in nunc, nunc vivamus. Cum arcu pretium, sed sed. In nonummy, tempor molestie id, omnis tellus. A risus dolor, vitae et donec, mauris amet posuere. Donec in, nonummy dolor luctus. Laoreet ligula, pretium nisl eleifend, malesuada tincidunt cursus. Congue velit iaculis.</p>
<blockquote><p>Tincidunt varius sequi, integer magna ac, donec curabitur. Rhoncus sed. Lectus vitae augue, mauris tincidunt. Ut nec fermentum, dolor vestibulum. Nunc neque tincidunt, non dictumst tempus. Et id, duis sit arcu, felis porta donec. Proin tincidunt.</p>
<p><strong> Egestas at amet. Pharetra mauris. </strong>Mattis quam feugiat, iure ipsum. Vel fringilla, accumsan nam rhoncus, orci diam. Aenean sit sodales, urna porttitor. Nulla enim consequat, amet congue. Mauris vulputate, nonummy vel.</p></blockquote>
<p>Phasellus lorem aliquam, pede morbi, nulla sed. Urna ut a. Mattis viverra dignissim, suspendisse risus, felis a. Sit nec. Sit egestas condimentum. Tempor quisque sit, commodo justo consequat. Augue fermentum, est vulputate et, purus et. Tincidunt quam enim, ac a pede.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/publishers-combine-forces-to-lure-advertisers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
