<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Travel &#8211; News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/category/travel/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 16:20:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The world&#8217;s best airport &#8211; Singapore Changi Airport</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/the-worlds-best-airport-singapore-changi-airport/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/the-worlds-best-airport-singapore-changi-airport/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 10:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[airport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=91</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hamad International Airport in Doha, Qatar, has been voted the Best Airport in the World at the Skytrax 2021 World Airport Awards, ending Singapore Changi Airport’s eight-year reign at the top. This year, the World Airport Awards have recognized the efforts of global airports in adapting and meeting the challenges of the Covid-19 pandemic, with [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hamad International Airport in Doha, Qatar, has been voted the Best Airport in the World at the Skytrax 2021 World Airport Awards, ending Singapore Changi Airport’s eight-year reign at the top.</p>
<p>This year, the World Airport Awards have recognized the efforts of global airports in adapting and meeting the challenges of the Covid-19 pandemic, with the past 18 months officially recognized as the most financially difficult period on record.</p>
<div class="code-block code-block-1"><ins id="revive-0-2" data-revive-zoneid="118" data-revive-ct0="%c" data-revive-id="7d3eab13b195263024792b3b73763e23" data-revive-seq="2" data-revive-loaded="1" data-revive-retina="1.5"></p>
<div id="beacon_153a2ba932"><img loading="lazy" src="https://adverts.ukimediaevents.com/www/delivery/lg.php?bannerid=0&amp;campaignid=0&amp;zoneid=118&amp;loc=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.passengerterminaltoday.com%2Fnews%2Fairport%2Fchangi-loses-crown-as-best-airport-in-the-world.html&amp;referer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.google.com%2F&amp;cb=153a2ba932" alt="" width="0" height="0" /></div>
<p></ins></div>
<p>Airports across the globe have invested to provide the safest possible environment for their customers and staff during the pandemic, although events have impacted some regions and airports more than others, with many areas having few, if any, international routes operating for more than a year.</p>
<p>Badr Mohammed Al-Meer, chief operating officer at Hamad International Airport (HIA), said, “This is not only a truly remarkable achievement for HIA and the state of Qatar, but an endorsement from our travelers for our commitment to service excellence. HIA continues to serve as a global benchmark for airports around the world, thanks to the dedication and collaboration of our team and stakeholders. To this day, HIA’s crisis preparedness, business continuity strategy, and agile and effective response to the Covid-19 pandemic continue to be recognized by leading industry institutions. As we look toward the future, HIA remains devoted to boosting our efforts in providing the best airport experience to all our passengers.”</p>
<p>Hamad International rounded off its success at the 2021 World Airport Awards by winning the awards for the Best Airport in the Middle East, the World’s Best Airport in the 25 to 35 million Passenger category, and for the Best Airport Staff in the Middle East.</p>
<p>Edward Plaisted, CEO of Skytrax, said, “We are delighted to announce that HIA has been voted the World’s Best Airport 2021. Inaugurated in 2014, Hamad International Airport has rapidly become a customer favorite and moved from No. 3 in the world in 2020 to be ranked World’s Best Airport this year. Achieving this honor is very much a team effort, and our congratulations go to the management, staff and stakeholders at Hamad International Airport that help make this happen. As travel hubs worldwide have been impacted by the pandemic, Hamad International Airport was undeterred by the global travel disruptions and continued with its expansion plans while introducing additional airport health and safety standards. As it is the Official Airport Partner for the FIFA World Cup Qatar 2022, we wish Hamad International Airport every success in helping to host such a major event.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/the-worlds-best-airport-singapore-changi-airport/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ryanair could offer $15 flights from the US to Europe</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/ryanair-could-offer-15-flights-from-the-us-to-europe/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/ryanair-could-offer-15-flights-from-the-us-to-europe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 10:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ryanair]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=84</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ryanair, known mostly for its risqué ads and abysmal customer service, has announced it plans to expand to the U.S. The budget airline, which primarily operates throughout Western Europe, is trying to capture a slice of the hugely profitable transatlantic market dominated by legacy carriers. “The board of Ryanair, like any PLC, have approved the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="speakable">Ryanair, known mostly for its risqué ads and abysmal customer service, has announced it plans to expand to the U.S.</p>
<p class="speakable">The budget airline, which primarily operates throughout Western Europe, is trying to capture a slice of the hugely profitable transatlantic market dominated by legacy carriers.</p>
<p>“The board of Ryanair, like any PLC, have approved the business plans for future growth, including transatlantic. We are talking to manufacturers about long-haul aircraft but can’t comment further on this,” a spokesperson for the airline told <a href="http://skift.com/2015/03/17/thus-the-fight-begins-ryanair-is-coming-to-the-u-s/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Skift.</a> “European consumers want lower cost travel to the USA and the same for Americans coming to Europe. We see it as a logical development in the European market.”</p>
<p>Ryanair said it would offer promotional fares—as low as £10 or $15 —from select American cities to London to shake up the old guard.  But don&#8217;t get too excited.  Regular prices would run about $200 to $300, and then there are the slew of fees, including charges to reserve seats and airline ticket printing.</p>
<p>The airline plans to offer flights between as many as 14 European cities and 12 to 14 U.S. cities. While the plan is still in its infant stages, we could see Ryanair stateside in about five years.</p>
<p>According to IATA data, the transatlantic market is considered the “jewel of the aviation industry,” accounting for over 16 percent of global airline traffic and a whopping 55 percent of revenue.  Despite an open-skies deal signed between the European Union and the U.S. in 2007, budget carriers have not figured out a model that allows them to compete.</p>
<p>But flying across Europe, with its notoriously cramped seats and scaled down amenities, may not be like flying across the pond.</p>
<p>The carrier plans to buy a fleet of 50 brand new aircraft that will feature a business class section, which doesn&#8217;t exist on its European service.  These could include fuel-efficient, modern planes, such as the Boeing Dreamliner and Airbus A350, but it all depends on when the carrier could get them, because manufacturing demand for these aircraft has soared.</p>
<p>But, Ryanair may be dependent on the use of second-tier airports—usually miles away from the major city hubs—which allows for greater airline efficiency and helps significantly cut costs.  U.S. airline consolidation has reduced capacity at these smaller markets, but customers, especially business travelers, may see these locations as less desirable.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/ryanair-could-offer-15-flights-from-the-us-to-europe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google Flights — database of air travel information</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/google-flights-database-of-air-travel-information/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/google-flights-database-of-air-travel-information/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 09:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Tech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Google]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=64</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There are plenty of search engines out there to find a cheap flight. Maybe you’ve got a favorite tool like Skyscanner, Hopper, or an online travel agency like Priceline or Expedia. But one option is better than all the rest: Google Flights. Yes, that’s right, the search engine behemoth is also king when it comes to [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are plenty of search engines out there to find a cheap flight. Maybe you’ve got a favorite tool like Skyscanner, Hopper, or an online travel agency like Priceline or Expedia. But one option is better than all the rest: <strong>Google Flights.</strong></p>
<p>Yes, that’s right, the search engine behemoth is also king when it comes to finding cheap flights. It’s incredibly powerful, with tons of features that will help you zero in on the best price. And it’s got a bevy of filters you can use to narrow down to the flights you really want … and avoid the ones you don’t. Plus, you can use this tool to search almost all carriers and book directly with an airline rather than through a third party – something that’s <a href="https://thriftytraveler.com/news/travel/coronavirus-lesson-ota/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">more important than ever right now</a>.</p>
<p>We’ll show you some of the best tips and tricks to book your next cheap flight at the lowest price. When you’re done, you’ll never use another flight search engine again.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/google-flights-database-of-air-travel-information/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>World&#8217;s biggest aircraft gets closer to takeoff</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/worlds-biggest-aircraft-gets-closer-to-takeoff/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/worlds-biggest-aircraft-gets-closer-to-takeoff/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 09:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Tech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[airlander]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=55</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The hefty, double-bodied Stratolaunch airplane — its wingspan of 385 feet (117 meters) is the widest in the world — recently reached a new milestone that brings it one step closer to leaving the ground. In runway tests conducted on Sunday (Feb. 25) at the Mojave Air and Space Port in Mojave, California, Stratolaunch achieved [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The hefty, double-bodied Stratolaunch airplane — its wingspan of 385 feet (117 meters) is the widest in the world — recently reached a new milestone that brings it one step closer to leaving the ground.</p>
<p>In runway tests conducted on Sunday (Feb. 25) at the Mojave Air and Space Port in Mojave, California, Stratolaunch achieved a taxi speed of 46 mph (74 km/h), according <a class="hawk-link-parsed" href="https://twitter.com/PaulGAllen/status/968168785076142080" data-url="https://twitter.com/PaulGAllen/status/968168785076142080" data-component-tracked="1">to a tweet</a> posted on Feb. 26 by Paul Allen, founder of Stratolaunch Systems Corp. and co-founder of Microsoft.</p>
<aside class="hawk-nest hawk-processed" data-render-type="fte" data-skip="dealsy" data-widget-type="seasonal" data-widget-id="efa25e23-9ef6-4a25-9e40-fa5bfd749c66" data-result="missing" data-feat-ref="hawk-id-0"></aside>
<p>Stratolaunch, which weighs about 500,000 lbs. (227,000 kilograms), can carry a payload of up to 550,000 lbs. (250,000 kg). The massive aircraft will transport rocket launchers and satellites bound for low Earth orbit, according to the company&#8217;s <a class="hawk-link-parsed" href="http://www.stratolaunch.com/" data-url="http://www.stratolaunch.com/" data-component-tracked="1">website</a>. [<a class="hawk-link-parsed" href="https://www.space.com/39155-stratolaunch-wprlds-largest-plane-test-photos.html" data-url="https://www.space.com/39155-stratolaunch-wprlds-largest-plane-test-photos.html" data-component-tracked="1">Stratolaunch Test Photos: The World&#8217;s Largest Plane in Action</a>]</p>
<div id="desktop-in-article" class="in-article ad-unit">
<div id="desktop-taboola-mid-article" class="trc_related_container trc_spotlight_widget trc_elastic trc_elastic_thumbnails-a-mid" data-placement-name="Mid Article">
<div class="trc_rbox_container">
<div>
<div id="trc_wrapper_96198" class="trc_rbox thumbnails-a-mid trc-content-sponsored ">
<div id="trc_header_96198" class="trc_rbox_header trc_rbox_border_elm">
<div class="trc_header_ext"></div>
</div>
<div id="outer_96198" class="trc_rbox_outer">
<div id="rbox-t2m" class="trc_rbox_div trc_rbox_border_elm">
<div id="internal_trc_96198">
<div class="videoCube trc_spotlight_item origin-undefined thumbnail_top syndicatedItem textItem videoCube_1_child trc-first-recommendation trc-spotlight-first-recommendation  trc_excludable " data-item-id="~~V1~~9090803356045862419~~cYINxacNH4CHgBlIhkRV7MiXX9tzI_Z-Q1NhET0E17rTxvAnL2wqac4MyzR7uD46gj3kUkbS3FhelBtnsiJV6MhkDZRZzzIqDobN6rWmCPA3hYz5D3PLat6nhIftiT1lwdxwdlxkeV_Mfb3eos_TQavImGhxk0e7psNAZxHJ9RJtvW5cjeP7iQeffKvooY_qPR29yes3rGOLyg-QiBU1MBE58TLMD7Cf-4darXwisAEGWHOQwDogJcAMaC2AsNmORdbgwlJdnqyroTPEQNNEnyrGgfXraZfkqzxVI8YJiN0" data-item-title="CAD Could Be Doomed As The Truth Comes Out" data-item-thumb="http://cdn.taboola.com/libtrc/static/thumbnails/b45db30123c65549a75714363f559e27.jpg" data-item-syndicated="true">
<div class=" trc_undo_btn "><span style="font-size: revert; color: initial;">Rocket launches from fixed locations can be delayed or halted by inclement weather and may face hazards from airborne traffic. But deploying rockets and satellites from a moving aircraft such as Stratolaunch — which would take off from a runway and release its payloads from a cruising altitude of about 36,000 feet (11,000 meters) — could reduce the risk of launch cancellations or delays from bad weather, making access to space &#8220;more convenient, reliable and routine,&#8221; Stratolaunch representatives said on the company </span><a class="hawk-link-parsed" style="font-size: revert;" href="http://www.stratolaunch.com/" data-url="http://www.stratolaunch.com/" data-component-tracked="1">website</a><span style="font-size: revert; color: initial;">.</span></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="jwplayer__widthsetter">
<div class="jwplayer__wrapper">
<div id="futr_botr_3hMIGpAD_UbKkvo80_div" class="future__jwplayer">
<div class="sticky-player-top-fade stick-on"></div>
<div class="sticky-player-background stick-on"></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>Stratolaunch resembles two conjoined airplanes connected by a central wing. It utilizes six Boeing 747 engines and has two fuselages, or aircraft bodies; the one on the right is occupied by the flight crew, and the one on the left houses flight data systems. The center wing that joins the fuselages helps to stabilize the aircraft and serves as the attachment point for rocket payloads, according to the Stratolaunch website.</p>
<p>Allen shared video of Stratolaunch on Feb. 26 as it trundled down the runway &#8220;with all flight surfaces in place,&#8221; he wrote on Twitter.</p>
<p>Stratolaunch first <a class="hawk-link-parsed" href="https://www.livescience.com/59324-largest-aircraft-stratolaunch-rolled-out.html" data-url="https://www.livescience.com/59324-largest-aircraft-stratolaunch-rolled-out.html" data-component-tracked="1">left its hangar</a> in May 2017, and in September, the aircraft&#8217;s engines were tested <a class="hawk-link-parsed" href="https://www.livescience.com/60497-worlds-largest-aircraft-stratolaunch-engine-tests.html" data-url="https://www.livescience.com/60497-worlds-largest-aircraft-stratolaunch-engine-tests.html" data-component-tracked="1">for the first time</a>. The plane first <a class="hawk-link-parsed" href="https://www.livescience.com/61236-stratolaunch-aircraft-taxi-test.html" data-url="https://www.livescience.com/61236-stratolaunch-aircraft-taxi-test.html" data-component-tracked="1">rolled down the runway</a> in December 2017, reaching a runway taxi speed of 40 mph (64 km/h) as technicians put the plane through its paces for steering and braking. The latest tests build on its prior runway performance, and the plane is expected to be operational by the end of the decade, according to company representatives.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/worlds-biggest-aircraft-gets-closer-to-takeoff/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Astronauts capture vivid Aurora display from International Space Station</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/astronauts-capture-vivid-aurora-display-from-international-space-station/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/astronauts-capture-vivid-aurora-display-from-international-space-station/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 08:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aurora]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ISS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=39</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Astronauts got to see an amazing display of southern lights over New Zealand and Antarctica earlier this month. Spectacular images and footage of the green-hued aurora flowed from the International Space Station, where the Expedition 66 crew got a view of the Indian Ocean show and shared it on social media(opens in new tab). &#8220;I caught this [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Astronauts got to see an amazing display of southern lights over New Zealand and Antarctica earlier this month.</p>
<p>Spectacular images and footage of the green-hued aurora flowed from the <a class="hawk-link-parsed" href="https://www.space.com/16748-international-space-station.html" data-component-tracked="1">International Space Station</a>, where the Expedition 66 crew got a view of the Indian Ocean show and shared it on <a class="hawk-link-parsed" href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/nasa2explore/51588972667/in/photostream/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-url="https://www.flickr.com/photos/nasa2explore/51588972667/in/photostream/" data-component-tracked="1">social media<span class="sr-only">(opens in new tab)</span></a>.</p>
<aside class="hawk-nest hawk-processed" data-render-type="fte" data-skip="dealsy" data-widget-type="seasonal" data-widget-id="9450f235-f161-44fc-b197-28802968c35e" data-result="missing" data-feat-ref="hawk-id-0"></aside>
<p>&#8220;I caught this aurora just as orbital sunrise was beginning. Breathtaking!&#8221; wrote NASA astronaut Shane Kimbrough on Oct. 12, two days after the show took place. With his tweet came a sweeping view of auroras over the barely lit limb of the <a class="hawk-link-parsed" href="https://www.space.com/54-earth-history-composition-and-atmosphere.html" data-component-tracked="1">Earth</a>.</p>
<div id="desktop-in-article" class="in-article ad-unit">
<div id="desktop-taboola-mid-article" class="trc_related_container trc_spotlight_widget trc_elastic trc_elastic_thumbnails-a-mid" data-placement-name="Mid Article">
<div class="trc_rbox_container">
<div>
<div id="trc_wrapper_23824" class="trc_rbox thumbnails-a-mid trc-content-sponsored ">
<div id="trc_header_23824" class="trc_rbox_header trc_rbox_border_elm">
<div class="trc_header_ext"></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>Auroras take place when charged particles from the sun, known as the <a class="hawk-link-parsed" href="https://www.space.com/22215-solar-wind.html" data-component-tracked="1">solar wind</a>, flow along the magnetic field lines of Earth and interact with our atmosphere. As the particles are <a class="hawk-link-parsed" href="https://www.space.com/15139-northern-lights-auroras-earth-facts-sdcmp.html" data-component-tracked="1">deflected by the magnetic field</a> to our planet&#8217;s poles, their interactions with the atmosphere dumps in energy and causes the atmosphere to glow.</p>
<div id="bordeaux-static-slot-16" class="bordeaux-slot" data-feat-ref="bordeaux-feat-id-107"></div>
<figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check="">
<div class="image-full-width-wrapper">
<div class="image-widthsetter">
<p class="vanilla-image-block"><picture><source class="expandable lazy-image-van" type="image/webp" data-normal="https://vanilla.futurecdn.net/space/media/img/missing-image.svg" data-srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-320-80.jpg.webp 320w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-480-80.jpg.webp 480w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-650-80.jpg.webp 650w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-970-80.jpg.webp 970w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-1024-80.jpg.webp 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-1200-80.jpg.webp 1200w" data-sizes="(min-width: 1000px) 970px, calc(100vw - 40px)" data-original-mos="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL.jpg" data-pin-media="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL.jpg" /><source class="expandable lazy-image-van" type="image/jpeg" data-normal="https://vanilla.futurecdn.net/space/media/img/missing-image.svg" data-srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-320-80.jpg 320w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-480-80.jpg 480w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-650-80.jpg 650w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-970-80.jpg 970w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-1024-80.jpg 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-1200-80.jpg 1200w" data-sizes="(min-width: 1000px) 970px, calc(100vw - 40px)" data-original-mos="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL.jpg" data-pin-media="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL.jpg" /></picture></p>
<figure class="expandable-image"><img class="expandable lazy-image-van loaded" src="https://vanilla.futurecdn.net/space/media/img/missing-image.svg" sizes="(min-width: 1000px) 970px, calc(100vw - 40px)" srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-320-80.jpg 320w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-480-80.jpg 480w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-650-80.jpg 650w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-970-80.jpg 970w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-1024-80.jpg 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-1200-80.jpg 1200w" alt="aurora" data-normal="https://vanilla.futurecdn.net/space/media/img/missing-image.svg" data-srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-320-80.jpg 320w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-480-80.jpg 480w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-650-80.jpg 650w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-970-80.jpg 970w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-1024-80.jpg 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL-1200-80.jpg 1200w" data-sizes="(min-width: 1000px) 970px, calc(100vw - 40px)" data-original-mos="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL.jpg" data-pin-media="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/qouZTvsmXj4b9Wx7cMtyuL.jpg" data-ll-status="loaded" /></p>
<div class="expand icon icon-expand-image"></div>
</figure>
</div>
</div><figcaption class=" inline-layout"><span class="caption-text">A stunning aurora rips over the Indian Ocean on Oct. 10, 2021, as seen by International Space Station astronauts. Credit: NASA </span><span class="credit">(Image credit: NASA)</span></figcaption></figure>
<div class="see-more see-more--clipped">
<div class="see-more__button-container"><span style="font-size: revert; color: initial;">The sun is somewhat near the </span><a class="hawk-link-parsed" style="font-size: revert;" href="https://www.space.com/the-mysterious-sunspots" data-component-tracked="1">beginning of a solar cycle</a><span style="font-size: revert; color: initial;">, which lasts about 11 years. Each cycle has a &#8220;maximum,&#8221; at which point there is more solar activity manifested as solar flares and coronal mass ejections, which can cause auroras if any particles flow in the right direction towards Earth.</span></div>
</div>
<div id="bordeaux-static-slot-11" class="bordeaux-slot" data-feat-ref="bordeaux-feat-id-102"></div>
<p>While we&#8217;re not near that maximum phase right now, the astronauts had a great viewpoint from their orbit at approximately 250 miles (400 km) above Earth, with no interfering atmosphere in the way. That said, French astronaut Thomas Pesquet said eventually the sun stopped observations.</p>
<div id="bordeaux-static-slot-12" class="bordeaux-slot" data-feat-ref="bordeaux-feat-id-103"></div>
<p>&#8220;The view in this #timelapse passes the #aurora to marvel at the stars and then be overwhelmed by a sunrise,&#8221; Pesquet wrote in a <a class="hawk-link-parsed" href="https://twitter.com/Thom_astro/status/1449802830232137734?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-url="https://twitter.com/Thom_astro/status/1449802830232137734?s=20" data-component-tracked="1">tweet<span class="sr-only">(opens in new tab)</span></a> posted on Sunday (Oct. 17).</p>
<div id="bordeaux-static-slot-13" class="bordeaux-slot" data-feat-ref="bordeaux-feat-id-104"></div>
<p>Although the aurora is beautiful, it could accompany a real danger for astronauts: radiation. NASA has <a class="hawk-link-parsed" href="https://www.space.com/moon-radiation-dose-for-astronauts-measured" data-component-tracked="1">lifetime radiation</a> protocols in place for its spaceflyers to protect against ill effects of radiation events in orbit, which can be associated with conditions such as cancer. The agency is also investigating the <a class="hawk-link-parsed" href="https://www.space.com/mars-radiation-obstacle-crewed-human-missions.html" data-component-tracked="1">exposure for astronauts</a> at future spaceflight destinations such as the moon and Mars.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/astronauts-capture-vivid-aurora-display-from-international-space-station/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Virtual swim with the dolphins</title>
		<link>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/virtual-swim-with-the-dolphins/</link>
					<comments>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/virtual-swim-with-the-dolphins/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kamal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 08:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dolphins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.theme-junkie.com/mystery/?p=42</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If you’ve run out of ways to destress at home, maybe it’s time to learn a trick or two from some laidback pals of ours in the sea. Models of happiness and innocence, dolphins always have that chilled AF look about them, and now you can paddle by their side thanks to a 360-degree virtual-reality experience on [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you’ve run out of ways to destress at home, maybe it’s time to learn a trick or two from some laidback pals of ours in the sea. Models of happiness and innocence, dolphins always have that chilled AF look about them, and now you can paddle by their side thanks to a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jAZsD3DgLjE">360-degree virtual-reality experience on YouTube</a>.</p>
<p>Created as part of a research programme into ‘dolphin-assisted therapy’, the two-minute clip was shot by Dutch non-profit <a href="https://thedolphinswimclub.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dolphin Swim Club</a> during a seven-day shoot in the Red Sea. In it, pods of spinner and bottlenose dolphins glide past the cameras, which you can swivel using a control pad to the top left of the screen: the fun lies in trying catch them before they vanish into the deep blue.</p>
<div id="inline-placement"></div>
<div class="anyclip-container">
<div class="ac-widget-placeholder ac-reset" data-loaded-pid="timeoutcomnewyork" data-loaded-wid="001w000001Y8Vax_7252">
<div id="ac-lre-player-ph-ext-teWaeO9ZKPT7bO55Tw5osHt8qz0XM8GU" class="ac-lre-player-ph-ext ac-lre-ph-playlist-hide-scroll-bar">
<div id="ac-lre-player-ph-teWaeO9ZKPT7bO55Tw5osHt8qz0XM8GU" class="h001w000001Y8Vax_7252 d001w000001Y8Vax_7252 vjs-hide-top-articles">
<div class="w001w000001Y8Vax_7252 luminous-theme is-floated-outer-title">
<div class="ac-player-ph">
<div class="ac-player-wrapper">
<div class="ac-lre-player vjs-flag-ads vjs-flag-ads-hide-controls">
<div id="ac-lre-vjs-teWaeO9ZKPT7bO55Tw5osHt8qz0XM8GU" class="video-js vjs-default-skin ac-lre-vjs-teWaeO9ZKPT7bO55Tw5osHt8qz0XM8GU-dimensions vjs-fluid vjs-controls-enabled vjs-workinghover vjs-v7 vjs-has-started vjs-layout-medium lx-size-1 cc-hidden vjs-user-inactive vjs-paused" lang="en-gb" tabindex="-1" role="region" translate="no" aria-label="Video Player">
<div class="lre-vjs-video-title-block lre-title-container">
<div class="lre-title-text">
<div class="lre-title-text-content">Just a standard Thursday night at the Market! Swing by for live music every Thursday in summer from&#8230;</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="vjs-text-track-display" translate="yes" aria-live="off" aria-atomic="true"></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>The research firm’s idea was to bring the joy of swimming with dolphins to disabled people and others who aren’t able to travel. They’ve since developed special ‘Underwater VR’ headsets that can be strapped on to patients in pools so they can ‘swim with dolphins’ without having to use animals in captivity (which has been criticised by environmentalists as cruel).</p>
<p>As treatments for stress go, it’s certainly pretty out-there. And though clinical trials are yet to take place, more than a thousand universities, hospitals and community centres around the world now use their ‘Dolphin VR’ programme as a general relaxation therapy, while similar technology is <a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC5421394/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">already playing a significant role in treatments for anxiety and other mental health problems</a>. We’d like some VR koala cuddles next, please.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://kchaudhary0868.github.io/news/2015/03/19/virtual-swim-with-the-dolphins/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
